http://aerva.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICYAerva is strongly committed to protecting your privacy and providing a safe online experience for all our users. This Privacy Policy applies to information collected online through Aerva's website, and Aerva’s software registration/account creation process and governs online data collection and usage by Aerva. Please read the complete Aerva Privacy Policy below and contact us if you have any questions.Changes to the Privacy PolicyWe reserve the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy. Since any changes will be posted on this page, we encourage you to check this page regularly. Your continued use of the Site following any changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes. Information We CollectWe may collect "personally identifiable information" from you such as your name, company name, postal address, telephone number, and e-mail address. We will collect personally identifiable information from you when you actively give us the information such as when you fill out online site registration forms or during user account creation for Aerva’s software use.We may collect "non-personally identifiable information" such as your Web site browsing patterns, IP address or demographic information. We collect non-personally identifiable information from you by "passive" means, often through the use of cookies.How We Use Your InformationWe will use your personally identifiable information for customer service, to provide you with information that you may request, and to customize your experience on the Site or to customize your software user experience. We may also combine the information we have gathered about you with information from other sources to better serve your needs. We may use third-party contractors to help us operate our business, the Site and our software and may share your information with these contractors for those limited purposes. Any e-mail messages we send will also provide you with an opportunity to opt-out. Please note that changes to your preferences may not be effective immediately. We will not share your personally identifiable information with third parties (other than in connection with the sale of our business or as noted above), unless you allow us to.We use non-personally identifiable information for internal purposes, to help us interact with visitors to the Site and to provide you with a good user experience when using our software. We may also share non-personally identifiable information in the aggregate form with third parties to illustrate trends and patterns. In the event that all of our business assets are transferred to or acquired by another company, your information will be one of the transferred assets. We will divulge your personal information to law enforcement officials if required to do so.LinksThe Site contains links to other sites, including, among others, those of advertisers, other third parties and companies whose trademarks may appear on the Site. We are not responsible for the information-collection practices or the content of the sites to which we link.Terms and ConditionsYou should assume that everything you see or read on the Site is copyrighted unless otherwise noted and may not be used except as provided in these Terms and Conditions or in the text on the Site without the written permission of Aerva. Aerva neither warrants nor represents that your use of materials displayed on the Site will not infringe rights of third parties not owned by or affiliated with Aerva.Aerva uses reasonable efforts to include accurate and up-to-date information in the Site. Aerva makes no warranties or representations as to its accuracy. Aerva assumes no liability or responsibility for any errors or omissions in the content of the Site.Images of people or places displayed on the Site are either the property of, or used with permission by, Aerva. The use of these images by you, or anyone else authorized by you, is prohibited unless specifically permitted by these Terms and Conditions or specific permission provided elsewhere on the Site. Any unauthorized use of the images may violate copyright laws, trademark laws, the laws of privacy and publicity, and communications regulations and statutes.The trademarks, logos, and service marks (collectively the "Trademarks") displayed on the Site are registered and unregistered Trademarks of Aerva and others. Nothing contained on the Site should be construed as granting, by implication, estoppels, or otherwise, any license or right to use any Trademarks displayed on the Site. Your misuse of the Trademarks displayed on the Site, or any other content on the Site, except as provided in these Terms and Conditions, is strictly prohibited. You are also advised that Aerva will aggressively enforce its intellectual property rights to the fullest extent of the law, including the seeking of criminal prosecution.Contact UsPlease contact us with any questions or comments regarding our privacy policy or terms and conditions:Aerva by Watchfire1015 Maple St.Danville, IL 61832USA
Content ManagementBrowser-BasedAny LayoutDynamic DataPowerful SchedulerSocial Media IntegrationUCG ModerationWYSIWYGContentNetwork ManagementCloud-BasedFlexible HardwareScalabilityMulti-UserSecurityReportingPlayer ScreenshotsHardware ControlNetwork Set-upNetworksCampusOut-of-HomeGovernmentCorporateTransitRetailThoughtsBlog | Videos | eBooks
